正体不明の犯人からワクチンを奪うために
We've infiltrated the Fukuma Denjo Hotel to steal a viral remedy from an unidentified bad guy.
僕らは伏魔殿上ホテルに潜入
タイムリミットは１時間
We have one hour.
間に合わないと　みんなが死んでしまう
If we don't make it in time, they'll all die!
意外とプロって普通なんだね
You seem pretty average for a pro, huh?
ガラスとか頭蓋骨なら　俺でも割れるよ
Breaking glass, busting skulls?
I can do that much.
But if your opening move is to call in reinforcements,
ていうか　即行　仲間呼んじゃうあたり
中坊とタイマンはるのも怖い人
I guess that means you're too scared to take on a junior-high kid alone.
いいだろうぬ
Very well-eth.
試してやるぬ
Let's see what you can do-eth.
じゃあ　遠慮なく
If you insist...
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
起立
礼
ロックオン
起立
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
礼
ロックオン
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
せんせー
ターゲットオン
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ポテンシャル高い
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
We've got a lot of potential
potential takai
ポテンシャル高い
ほどめんどくさい
It's just that we're not trying
hodo mendokusai
ほどめんどくさい
总监.Maki
台本.小伍
ほどめんどくさい
We had that dropouts' mentality
dropout mentality
ほどめんどくさい
ドロップアウト　メンタリティー
No matter the unusual situation we were in
hinichijou wo ryougashi
翻译.兰樱
非日常を凌駕し
校对.Maki
翻译.兰樱
非日常を凌駕し
校对.Maki
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
We pretended to doze off
bokura wa utatanegao shite
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
While holding on to a hidden knife
knife kakushimotta
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
僕らはうたたね顔して
时间轴.歪歪
BDRip.VCB-Studio
ナイフ隠し持った
起立
Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on
礼
ロックオン
Thinking someone would deal with you eventually
hottokeba kitto dareka yatte kureru to
ほっとけば　きっと誰か　やってくれると
We didn't really feel invested in the job
doko ka taningoto datta
どこか　他人事だった
だけど
But now
dakedo
だけど
Teacher, teach us, we're still growing up
mister teacher oshiete mikansei na bokura
Mr.ティーチャー教えて　未完成の僕ら
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
Will we be able to shoot through an invincible target like you?
anata to iu furaku no target uchinukeru deshou ka
あなたという不落のターゲット　撃抜けるでしょうか
As long as we challenge you, it's fifty-fifty
Stand, bow, lock on!
idomu kagiri kanousei wa half and half
kiritsu rei lock on
挑む限り　可能性はハーフ＆ハーフ
Teacher, watch us, as we try to find a direction in life
mister teacher mite ite mayoi ooki bokura
Mr.ティーチャー見ていて　迷い多き僕ら
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
We're studying our ass off for you more than anybody else
dare yori mo anata no tame ni moubenkyouchuu sa
誰よりもあなたのために猛勉強中さ
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
Only the bloodlust is our message to you
satsui dake ga anata e no message
Stand, bow, lock on! Stand, bow, lock on!
kiritsu rei lock on kiritsu rei lock on
殺意だけが　あなたへのメッセージ
We'll make our dreams come true on our own for real
jiriki gachi de hongan iku yo
自力　ガチで
本願　行くよ
A revolution!
revolution
レボリューション
Oh yeah!
oh yeah
せんせー
The target is our teacher!
sensei target on
せんせー
ターゲットオン
Episode
Karma
Time
2nd
Period
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 及微博 @诸神字幕组
Too soft-eth. You'll have to find-eth a better weapon.
柔いぬ　もっといい武器を探すべきだぬ
Don't need one.
必要ないね
Grip strength capable of crushing skulls...
頭蓋骨を握りつぶすほどの握力
一度つかまれたら　ゲームオーバー
Once he gets his hands on me, it's game over.
On first glance, this seems like an unwinnable game,
普通に考えて　無理ゲーだけど
立場が逆なだけで
but just switch our positions around,
and it's no different from the unwinnable game we always play.
いつもやってんだよね　その無理ゲー
すごい
Wow...
全部よけるか　さばいてる
He's dodging or blocking every blow!
烏間先生の防御テクニックですね
That's your defense technique, right, Karasuma-sensei?
殺し屋にとって　防御技術は優先度が低い
Self-defense is low priority for assassins,
だから　授業で教えた覚えはないが…
so while I don't remember teaching it in class,
he must have picked it up by
watching me dodge their knives.
目で見て盗んだな
俺が生徒のナイフをよける動きを
赤羽業　このＥ組でも戦闘の才能は頭一つ抜けている
Akabane Karma... Even in this E Class,
his talent for fighting is head and shoulders above the rest.
I can dodge him... but if I move in to attack, he'll grab me.
よけられるけど　こっちから攻め込んだら捕まるからな
What's wrong-eth?
どうしたぬ
攻撃しなくては永久にここを抜けられぬぞぬ
You'll never get past me if you don't attack-eth!
You think?
どうかな
あんたを引き付けるだけ引き付けといて
I mean, I could be doing my best to distract you
その隙に　みんながちょっとずつ抜けるってのもありかと思って
while the rest of us slip past, a few at a time.
安心しなよ
But relax.
No underhanded shenanigans here.
そんなこすいことはなしだ
今度は俺からいくからさ
Now... it's my turn.
Barehanded, like you.
あんたに合わせて　正々堂々
素手のタイマンで決着つけるよ
We'll settle this fair and square, man to man.
I like-eth that face of yours, young warrior.
いい顔だぬ　少年戦士よ
お前とならやれそうぬ
With you, I've got a chance—
暗殺稼業では味わえぬフェアな戦いがぬ
a chance to have-eth the kind of fair fight
I can't experience in the world of assassins.
チャンス
Now's my chance!
It's over-eth.
一丁上がりぬ
That gas!
あのガス…
長期戦は好まぬ
I'm not fond-eth of drawn-out fights.
スモッグの麻酔ガスを試してみることにしたぬ
So I thought I'd give-eth Smog's paralyzing gas a try.
き…汚え
That's dirty!
そんなもん隠し持っといて　どこがフェアだよ
Ain't nothin' fair about sneakin' that into the fight!
俺は一度も素手だけとは言ってないぬ
I never said that I only fight-eth bare-handed.
One mustn't get-eth too particular about one's hangups.
こだわることにこだわり過ぎないぬ
それもまたこの仕事を長くやっていく秘訣だぬ
That's another key to sticking around-eth in this business.
A spray of gas at point-blank range-eth...
至近距離のガス噴射
予期していなければ　絶対に防げ…
You'll never defend-eth against it if you don't see it com—
ぬ…ぬあん…だ…と…ぬ
Wh-What have you... hm...
Wow, what a coincidence!
奇遇だね　２人とも同じこと考えてた
Great minds think alike, huh?
How.... did you... get-eth... that...
なぜ…　お前がそれを…持っているぬ…
しかも…　なぜお前は…　俺のガスは吸ってないぬ…
And how... did you avoid-eth... breathing my gas...
Eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth!
C'mon, Terasaka, make it snappy!
ほら　寺坂　早く早く
We'll need duct tape and sheer numbers to beat this monster!
ガムテと人数使わないと　こんな化け物勝てないって
Yeah, I'm on it.
へー　へー
てめえが素手のタイマンの約束とか…
That promise of a barehanded one-on-one fight?
もっとないわな
It was bullshit from the word go!
Careful taping him up.
縛るとき　気を付けろ
そいつの怪力は　まひしていても要注意だ
With his superhuman strength,
you've got to be cautious even when he's paralyzed.
はーい
Yes, sir.
Eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth-eth...
I nicked an unused cartridge from that poisoner guy.
毒使いのおっさんが未使用だったのくすねたんだよ
使い捨てなのがもったいないくらい便利だね
Pretty handy. Shame they're one use only.
How-eth... did you see-eth my gas attack coming?
なぜだぬ…　俺のガス攻撃
お前は読んでいたから　吸わなかったぬ
Is that why you didn't breathe-eth any in?
俺は素手しか見せていないのにぬ
All I showed-eth you were my bare hands... So how-eth?
なぜぬ
Do I really need to say?
当然っしょ　素手以外の全部を警戒してたよ
I was on guard against everything but bare hands.
Hm...
あんたが素手の戦いをしたかったのはホントだろうけど
I'm sure you really did want a barehanded bout...
but you would have had to stop us by any means necessary,
俺らをここで止めるためにはどんな手段でも使うべきだし
and if I were you, I would've done the same.
俺でも　そっちの立場ならそうしてる
あんたのプロ意識を信じたんだよ
I had faith you'd fight like a true pro...
信じたから警戒してた
and that's why I was on guard.
なるほど
Oh, I get it!
業君　ちょっと変わったな
Karma-kun's changed... for the better.
いい感じに
大きな敗北を知らなかった業君は
He had never known true defeat,
期末テストで敗者となって　身をもって知ったでしょう
but those final exams taught him all too well:
Losers are people just like you who have their own lives, their own thoughts, and their own worries.
敗者だって自分と同じ　色々考えて生きている人間なんだと
それに気付いた者は必然的に
Once you realize that, you inevitably find
勝負の場で相手のことを見くびらないようになる
that you can no longer make light of your opponent on the battlefield.
自分と同じように敵も考えていないか　頑張っていないか
You see that your foe has their own motivations. That they're trying just as hard as you.
敵の能力や事情をちゃんと見るようになる
And you come to see their abilities. Their circumstances.
Someone who can be respectfully wary of their opponent...
敵に対し　敬意を持って警戒できる人
戦場では　そういう人を　隙がないと言うのです
leaves no openings on the battlefield.
一度の敗北を実に大きな糧にした
You grew so much from that one defeat.
You'll make a name for yourself someday.
君は将来　大物になれます
Seems you're a force to be
reckoned-eth with, young warrior.
大したやつだぬ　少年戦士よ
負けはしたが　楽しい時間を過ごせたぬ
I may have lost,
but I enjoyed our time toget—
えっ　何言ってんの
What are you talking about?
The fun's just beginning!
楽しいのこれからじゃん
Eth?
な…何だね　それは
What the hell-eth is that?
わさび＆からし
Wasabi and mustard. I'm gonna put them up your nostrils.
おじさんぬの鼻の穴にねじ込むの
えっ　何ぬ
What-eth?!
I'd been on guard around you all this time,
さっきまではきっちり警戒してたけど
こんだけ拘束したら　警戒もクソもないよね
but now that you're tied up, what's the point?
Eth?
Once these are in, I'll plug your nose with a special clip,
これ入れたら　専用クリップで鼻ふさいで
口の中にトウガラシの１０００倍辛いブートジョロキアぶち込んで
stuff your mouth with ghost peppers—a thousand times hotter than average chilis—
Be Prepared
その上から猿ぐつわして　処置完了
and then I'll gag you. Done and done!
Be Prepared
Now, my friend-eth...
さあ　おじさんぬ　今こそプロの意地を見せるときだぬ
It's time to show-eth me your willpower as a pro.
殺せんせー…　業君　特に変わってなくない
Korosensei...
Karma-kun hasn't really changed all that much, has he?
ええ　将来が思いやられます
No, he hasn't. I'm a little worried about his future.
What the hell did you bring with you, anyway?
何つうもん　持ってきてんだよ
Hey, let's get goin'. If we keep draggin' our feet, they'll find us.
おら行くぞ　もたもたしてっと見つかっちまう
ずうたいでかいからね
They'll find you, you big hulk.
うるせえ
Aw, shut it!
皆さん　この上がテラスです
Okay, everyone, the terrace is upstairs.
The bar floor. Could be tricky.
バーフロア　問題の階ね
はい
Yes.
There's a stairway to the VIP floor inside a lounge here.
Fukuma Denjo Hotel
Current Location
Display Route
You Are Here
ここからＶＩＰフロアへ通じる階段は店の奥にあります
The back entrance is locked,
裏口は鍵が掛かっているので
室内から侵入して　鍵を開けるしかありません
so we'll have to come in through the lounge to unlock it.
こっからはアドリブかぁ
Now we're flying by the seat of our pants.
We really stand out, though.
俺たちは目立っちまうな
先生たちはここで隠れてて
Let's have the guys hide here.
We'll sneak into the lounge and unlock the back entrance.
私たちが店に潜入して　中から裏口を開けるから
こういう所は　女子だけの方が怪しまれないでしょ
We girls won't look suspicious alone in a place like this.
No. You girls would be in too much danger on your own.
いや…　女子だけでは危険だ
Oh! In that case...
だったら…
Huh?
What beautiful stars!
星　奇麗
ね
Right?
All thanks to the CEO.
社長のおかげだな
ホント
You bet!
My folks' connections got me a room here.
親のコネで予約したホテル
Got my share of playmates—all with an eye on the family riches.
親の金目当てで相手してくれるやつはいるけど
Lame. What a lame-ass summer vacation.
カッコ悪い…
何てカッコ悪い夏休みだ
C'mon, be a man! Now get in front and protect us, Nagisa-kun!
ほら　男でしょ
ちゃんと前に立って守らないと　渚君
I can't! I can't be out in front!
無理　前に立つとか　絶対無理
Give it up!
諦めな
Go on!
ほら
Why me?
どうして…　僕が…
We'd like a guy around, but in places like this,
they check guys real carefully.
男手も欲しいけど　こういう所は男にチェック厳しいの
Yeah, but even so—
だからって…
It's all part of the plan!
作戦なんだから
Really?
本当に
ええ　本当です
Yes, really!
Not you too!
律まで
You're acting too normal. It's not fresh enough.
自然過ぎて新鮮味がない
そんな新鮮さ　いらないよ
But that's not what I'm looking for!
Where did you find these clothes, anyway?
どこにあったの　こんな服
外のプールサイドに脱ぎ捨ててあった
Someone left them next to the outdoor pool.
There's a nice one. I totally dig her awkwardness.
あの子　いいな　慣れてない感じが新鮮だ
Ugh! Let's get out of this filthy place ASAP!
やだやだ　こんな不潔な場所　さっさと抜けたいわ
At least you seem to be enjoying yourself, Fuwa-san.
そのわりには楽しそうだね　不破さん
Hey!
ねっ
Where'd you come from?
どっから来たの　君ら
そっちで俺と飲まねえ
How about a drink? Anything you like—
金あるから　何でもおごってやんよ
it's on me!
Go ahead, Nagisa! Keep him company!
はい　渚　相手しといて
Huh? But, Kataoka-san...
片岡さん
We have to act normal, remember?
怪しまれないように振る舞わないと　何かあったら呼ぶからさ
We'll come get you if anything happens.
How did it come to this?
何で　こんなことに
Oh, so you're Nagisa-chan! I'm Yuuji.
そっか　渚ちゃんっていうのか
俺　ユウジな
Okay! Now's our chance!
よし　今のうち
Let's see, the staircase to go up...
えっと　上への階段は…
It's got to be this way, right?
こっちで　間違いないわね
Hey, ladies.
よう　お嬢たち
On your own?
女だけ
How's about hangin' with us tonight?
俺らとどうよ　今夜
Oh, hell. Will it never end?
ったく　もう　次から次へ切りないな
Look, let me tell you something...
あのねぇ　言っときますけど…
Yada-san?
矢田さん
We'd love to hang out with cool guys like you,
お兄さんたち　カッコイイから遊びたいけど
but we're here with our daddies today.
あいにく今日はパパ同伴なの　私たち
And my daddy's kinda scary.
うちのパパ　ちょっと怖いから
So let's not.
やめとこ
な…　ヤ…ヤクザのエンブレム
A-A yakuza emblem!
And it's the infamous tiny-but-terrifyin' Shuuei Syndicate!
し…しかも　確か　少人数だけど　凶悪で有名な集英組…
I asked real nice and he gave this to me.
ねだったらくれちゃって　スクバのチャームにしよっかなって
Maybe I'll pin it on my schoolbag!
失礼しました
Sorry about that!
意気地なし　借り物に決まってるのにね
Wimps. It obviously wasn't mine.
That was amazing, Yada-san!
矢田さん　すごい
C'mon, drink up! I'm paying!
おら飲めよ
おごりだ　ぱーっとやろうぜ
We're gonna kick it tonight!
O-Oh, I'm more of a soda gu—er, girl.
いや　ぼ…　私は飲めないんで
I've got to try to act natural until the girls reach their goal.
女子チームが目的を果たすまで
不自然にならないようにつながないと
ユウジ君はさ…
Um, Yuuji-kun? Are you here with your parents?
親と来てるの
My parents?
親？
Like they have the time!
うちの親にそんな暇あるわけねえ
This is just between us, but my old man,
he's a famous TV personality.
ここだけの話な　俺の親父　テレビで有名なタレントなんだぁ
You've heard of him, believe me!
渚ちゃんも　絶対知ってるぜ
He's such a big deal he can get away with anything.
何やっても許される大物だからよ
この前なんか
He was bragging about having squeezed this
woman announcer's ass for 24 hours straight.
２４時間ずーっと女子アナのツーケー握り続けてたって自慢してたぜ
Does your dad have some kind of grudge against asses or something?
君のお父さん　ケツに何か恨みでもあるの
Dammit! You idiot, Yuuji!
くそ…　バカか　俺は
ナンパぐらい　親父に頼らずてめえの力でやれってんだ
Can't you hit on someone without leaning on the old man for once?
Uber-lame...
カッコ悪い…
That's... not a regular cigarette, is it?
それ　たばこじゃないよね　もっと危ない…
It's more dangerous than that.
Yeah. I just got into it.
ああ　最近　始めてよ
俺らの年で　こういうの知ってるやつがカッコイイんだぜ
At my age, if you know about these, you're cool.
Our teacher said he doesn't know if smoking those will make you cool,
学校の先生が言ってたよ
吸ってカッコ良くなるかどうかは知らないけど
確実に生きづらくはなるだろうって
but it definitely makes your life harder.
Life's already hard for us men!
生きづれえんだよ　男はもともと
We gotta force ourselves to try to look cool!
男はよ　無理にでもカッコ付けなきゃいけねえんだよ
And it's even worse for me 'cos I'm always getting compared to my old man!
俺みたく　いつも親と比較されてりゃ　なおさらな
You girls got it made.
お前ら女はいいよな
All you have to do is pick a cool guy.
最終的にはカッコイイ男選ぶだけでいいんだからよ
Um... yyyeah.
I think the girls in my class have a little more on their minds.
うちの女子はもうちょっとしっかり考えてると思うんだけど
Wow, you borrowed that from Bitch-sensei?
これ　ビッチ先生に借りたんだ
すごいよ　あの人は
She's something else. Yakuza, lawyer, racehorse owner...
ヤクザ　弁護士　馬主…
She's got every kind of pin you could think of,
仕事のとき使えるからって　あらゆるバッチ揃ってるの
since she can use them for her work.
You're always so interested in
Bitch-sensei's work, Yada-san.
そういや　矢田さんは一番熱心に聞いてるもんね　ビッチ先生の仕事の話
Yeah... It's not like I want to seduce people, though.
うん　色仕掛けがしたいわけじゃないけど
It's like what Korosensei said:
you gotta wield a second blade.
殺せんせーも言ってたじゃない
第二の刃を持てってさ
I'm betting her intimacy and negotiating skills
接待術も交渉術も　社会に出たとき　最高の刃になりそうじゃない
are probably your best bet out in the world.
Whoa, Yada-san. You're going to be one kickass grownup!
矢田さんはカッコイイ大人になるね
Even with those big boobs, I can't help but admire you!
巨乳なのに　ほれざるを得ない
The big-boob-hating Kayanocchi opens her heart!
巨乳を憎む茅野っちが心を開いた
Look, ladies!
みんな　あれ
We made it... but there's a lookout.
たどりついたはいいけど　見張りがいるのよね
We might need a man around after all.
場合によっちゃ　男手が必要かも
Yeah...
そうね
Kayano-san, go get Nagisa.
茅野さん　渚を呼んできて
Okay.
何とか　あの見張り　おびき出して
Think we can lure out that lookout and sneak past?
その隙に通れないかな
I'd rather not force our way through.
強行突破は避けたいよね
If we get the better of him, we'll be found out.
倒したら　すぐバレちゃう
Nagisa!
渚
Kayano!
茅野
Oh, um... I gotta go.
あっ　じゃあ　ぼ…　私　行くね
What? Already?
おい…　もうかよ
Bye now!
またね
Dammit! I can't let her get away without acting my coolest!
くっそ…　このまま　カッコ付けずに引き下がれるか
Did you have to leave me alone like that?
一人にしないでよ
ごめんごめん　作戦　決まったから
Sorry! We hammered out a strategy.
Great. I can't wait to get out of these clothes.
よかった…　早く着替えたいよ
おう　待てって　彼女ら
Hey, wait up, ladies!
As a special treat, check out my signature dance moves!
大サービスだ
俺のおはこのダンスを見せてやるよ
Go away.
邪魔…
I've been doing this ever since I was a kid.
がきのころからやってんだ
These moves always get me the girl!
こいつで女どもをわしづかみに…
Huh?
Hey, brat! Tough guy, eh?
こら　がき…　いい度胸だ
N-No... I—
あ…　いや…
ちっと来い
Get over here!
I didn't mean to—
今のはわざとじゃ…
This is a million-yen jacket. I demand compensation!
１００万する上着だぞ　弁償しろや
Your address, now!
ほら　住所　書け
やめて…
ひなたちゃん
Hinata-chan!
Add on pain and suffering, and that's three million total.
慰謝料込みで３００万
Pay up and we'll only leave you half dead!
それ払えば　半殺しで許してやる
What?! M-My father will pay! Please don't beat me up!
か…金は親父が出すから　殴るのは…
すみません　ヤクザさん
Excuse me, Mr. Yakuza, sir?
Yeah?
よっと
ほい　ほい　ほいっと
Excuse me, sir?
すみません　店の人
One of the patrons just suddenly collapsed.
あの人　急に倒れたみたいで
運び出して　みてあげてよ
You'd better get him out of harm's way and have him looked at.
Y-Yes, ma'am. Sorry for the bother.
はい　失礼しました
What'd he do, overdose? Sheesh.
ドラッグのきめ過ぎか　ったく…
Now!
今のうち
Back to the dance floor with you!
さあ　君もフロアに戻って
And don't tell anyone about this, okay?
今のこと　内緒ね
女子の方があっさりカッコイイことしちゃっても
Even when girls pull off something cool so effortlessly,
you still have to chin up and act cool yourself.
それでも　めげずにカッコ付けなきゃいけないから
It is hard, being a guy.
つらいよね　男子は
Nagisa-chan...
渚ちゃん…
If we meet again, keep acting cool, okay?
今度会ったら　またカッコ付けてよ
Though cut out the drugs and dancing if you can help it.
できれば　ドラッグとダンス以外がいいな
Here we are!
お待たせ
We really sent you into some dicey territory.
危険な場所へ潜入させてしまいましたね
You weren't in any danger, were you?
危ない目に遭いませんでしたか
Nuh-uh!
ううん
Not remotely!
ちっとも
Wow, you sure changed fast, Nagisa.
あれ　着替えるの早いね　渚
Yeah.
Hmm? What's wrong?
どうしたの
It's just...
いや…　結局　今回　女子が全部やってくれたし
You girls did everything this time around.
What was even the point of me being in this getup?
僕がこんな格好した意味って…
Comic relief, duh!
面白いからに決まってんじゃん
Don't you dare, Karma-kun!
撮らないでよ　業君
No, I don't think that's it.
そんなことないと思うよ
I'm sure it wound up helping someone.
きっと誰かのためになってるって
あのまま行けば　よかったのに
If only you could have stayed like that.
History's full of assassins who disguised themselves as women, after all.
暗殺者が女に化けるのは　歴史上でもよくあるぞ
い…磯貝君まで…
Don't you start too, Isogai-kun!
If you're gonna cut it off, Nagisa-kun, sooner is better.
渚君　取るなら　早い方がいいらしいよ
I am not! I happen to like it!
取らないよ　大事にするよ
Can we talk about this later?
その話は後にしてくれるか
Or never.
二度としません…
We're in our final stage of infiltration here.
この潜入も終盤だ
Ritsu?
律
Yes, sir.
はい
Up ahead is the VIP floor.
ここからは　ＶＩＰフロアです
These guests don't rely solely on hotel security
ホテルの者だけに警備を任せず
but provide their own hired lookouts.
客が個人で雇った見張りを置けるようです
So of course there's some blocking the staircase.
そんで　早速　上への階段に見張りか
超強そう
They look way tough, too.
Are they more of the guys who've been threatening us?
私たちを脅してるやつの一味なの
Or are they hired muscle that has nothing to do with us?
それとも無関係の人が雇った警備
Either way, we're gonna have to beat 'em to get by.
どっちでもいい　倒さなきゃ通れねえのは一緒だろうが
That's exactly right, Terasaka-kun.
そのとおり　寺坂君
And that weapon you have will do the job perfectly.
そして　倒すには君が持っている武器などが最適ですね
Pff! What, you got X-ray vision now, too?
透視能力でもあんのか　てめえは
You'll have to take them both down at the same time, or they'll call for help.
一瞬で２人とも仕留めないと　連絡されるぞ
I got this, okay?
任せてくれって
Hey, Kimura, see if you can lure 'em out this way some.
おい　木村　あいつらをちょっとここまで誘い出してこい
Who, me?
俺が　どうやって…
But how?
知らねえよ
How should I know?
Here, Kimura, try this...
じゃあ　こう言ってみ　木村
What gives, kid?
何だ　坊主
Huh? Any brains around here?
あれ　脳みそ君がいないなぁ
These guys are total muscleheads!
こいつらは頭の中まで筋肉だし
You slabs of pigmeat oughta quit pretending to be human.
人の形してんじゃねえよ　豚肉どもが
Hey!
おい
Get back here!
待て　こら
そりゃ怒るわ
Yep, that pissed 'em off!
What's with this brat?
何だ　このがき
He's crazy fast!
クソ速え
Okay! Now!
おっし…　今だ
Got it!
おう
ス…スタンガン
S-Stun-guns?
I bought 'em to see how electricity worked on that octopus.
タコに電気　試そうと思って買っといたのよ
こんな形でお披露目とは思わなかったけどな
Never thought I'd be usin' 'em like this!
買っといたって…　高かったでしょ　それ
You bought those? Weren't they expensive?
Huh? Uh, well...
いや…　最近ちょっと　臨時収入があったもんでよ
I came into a little money lately, so...
These two... They look...
こいつら　どこかで…
Nice weapon, Terasaka-kun.
いい武器です　寺坂君
But check their chests.
ですが　その２人の胸元を探ってください
Huh?
膨らみから察するに
Judging from the bulges there,
you ought to be able to find something even better.
もっといい武器が手に入るはずですよ
R-Real guns!
ほ…本物の銃
And...
そして　千葉君　速水さん
Chiba-kun? Hayami-san?
Those guns are for you.
この銃は君たちが持ちなさい
烏間先生は　まだ精密な射撃ができるところまで回復していない
Karasuma-sensei hasn't recovered enough to fire with any accuracy.
Right now, you two are the best gun-users we have.
今この中で最もそれを使えるのは　君たち２人です
B-But this is all so sudden.
だ…だからって　いきな…
However!
ただし　先生は殺すことは許しません
No Killing
I will not permit you to kill anyone.
With your skill, you should have plenty of ways to use those to defeat someone without a scratch.
君たちの腕前でそれを使えば
傷つけずに倒す方法は　いくらでもあるはずです
Giving us real guns?
When we couldn't even pull off our mission with airguns?
俺らが　本物の銃を…
Let's be on our way, then.
今日　エアガンでも失敗したのに
From the looks of things at this hotel,
さて　行きましょう
there's no sign the enemy has set up camp in any great numbers.
ホテルの様子を見るかぎり
They're probably down to one or two hired killers—at most.
敵が大人数で陣取っている気配はない
Yeah! So let's go murdalize the rest!
雇った殺し屋も　残りはせいぜい１人２人
Okay, team: we'll have to use the VIP-only
emergency stairs to reach the next floor up.
おう　さっさと行って　ぶち殺そうぜ
And to do that, we'll have to go through the concert hall on the 8th floor.
皆さん　これより上の階もＶＩＰ専用の非常階段を使わなくてはなりません
This is starting to leave a bad taste in my mouth.
I was charged with killing some super-creature,
そのためには　８階のコンサートホールを通り抜ける必要があります
so how'd I get stuck going to meet a bunch of kids?
味の悪い仕事になってきたぜ
Revolting.
超生物を殺す任務だったはずが
Sure enough, the only thing tasty around here...
いつの間にか　がきどものお出迎え
is my gun.
クソまずい
やっぱりうめえのは…
銃だけだ
太陽が射す　閉ざした瞼の裏側に赤い残像
The sun shines
taiyou ga sasu
On the back of my closed eyelids
tozashita mabuta no uragawa ni
I see red afterimages
akai zanzou
With a notebook and a pen in my leather bag
kawa no kaban ni nooto to pen wo
革の鞄に　ノートとペンを　さあ歩き出そう
I go for a walk
saa arukidasou
I keep drawing, but I can't get it to look pretty
kaitemo kaitemo kirei ni naranai
描いても描いても　綺麗にならない
My choice of colors is not to blame
eranda enogu ni tsumi wa nai
選んだ絵の具に　罪はない
I still remember the shooting star I saw last night
kinou no yonaka ni mita nagareboshi mada oboeteiru
昨日の夜中に見た流れ星　まだ覚えている
I was waiting for...
I was waiting for…
Hello shooting-star Hello shooting-star again
Hello, shooting star
Hello, shooting star, again
I was waiting
matteita yo
待っていたよ
夢を見るあの子はずっと
The girl of many dreams
yume wo miru ano ko wa zutto
ここにいるの　Ah　Ah
Is always here
koko ni iru no
あの日のまま　Ah　Ah
Just like you did that day
ano hi no mama
また光って
Shine again
mata hikatte
渚君　人にはＸＹと呼ばれる染色体があり
ＸとＹで男性　Ｘを２本持つと女性になります
子供は母親からＸを一本もらい　父親からＸかＹのどちらかをもらいます
つまり　子供の性別は父親からどちらをもらうかによって決まります
次回　暗殺教室　☓☓の時間